[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "CD", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 8, "question": "How high?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 9, "answer": "It's 147 over 89.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 12, "question": "How many push-ups can you do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 13, "answer": "Not enough.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 39, "question": "Why didn't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 40, "answer": "I guess I wanted to see him win.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 44, "question": "Playing mean every week -- I mean does that bring you joy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "NN", "DT", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 45, "answer": "It does.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 57, "question": "And I -- and I'm getting kind of worried that we're all going to have some kind of a society that has a narcissistic disorder, you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 58, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", "."], "qSentId": 65, "question": "Well, you know, part of the reason I wanted you to act -- to join us tonight was to talk about how wonderfully you have aged, all right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "VB", ":", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "WRB", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", ",", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 66, "answer": "Oh.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 83, "question": "What's the secret?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 84, "answer": "If you're just talking about pragmatic things, I like to hike.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 116, "question": "This deep psychic wound you refer to, is this the powerlessness you felt during your father's illness?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 117, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 150, "question": "Sleep?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 151, "answer": "You have suggestions for that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 172, "question": "Do you find yourself in a happy place?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 173, "answer": "Can I tell you that the moment I turned 50, I walked into my morning coffee shop and I -- you know, I never celebrate my birthdays.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 196, "question": "Do you think you're active for 30 minutes a day?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 197, "answer": "Yes, for the most part.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 200, "question": "Do you floss your teeth?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 201, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 202, "question": "You do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 203, "answer": "I love my dentist.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 208, "question": "Do you take -- do you take supplements?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", ":", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 209, "answer": "Not as much as I should.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 220, "question": "And did he have any other neurologic issues besides that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 221, "answer": "Yes, he did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 255, "question": "Do you take time to yourself?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 256, "answer": "Hell, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 267, "question": "How many pushups can you do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 268, "answer": "Not enough.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 285, "question": "Someone our age ought to be able to stand on one foot -- go on one foot, OK?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "PRP$", "NN", "MD", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "CD", "NN", ":", "IN", "IN", "CD", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 286, "answer": "Um-hmm.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NNS", ":", "WRB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NNS", ",", "RB", "DT", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 340, "question": "-- oh, God, they're incredibly vivid and they don't stop, which must mean that I'm not having a certain quality of sleep, is that correct?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 341, "answer": "Yes, later in the show, we're going to walk you through dreams -- why so many of us aren't having the right kinds, so all are troubled by the dreams that we have.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 360, "question": "Wasn't that fabulous?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "WDT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 361, "answer": "Oh, I remember that day.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 364, "question": "You were smashed?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 365, "answer": "It was so cold.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 389, "question": "AUPER: Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 390, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 398, "question": "How old does your lungs or your brain think you are?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 399, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "CC", "VBG", "CC", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 404, "question": "Just doing stuff?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 405, "answer": "I was doing work, you know, meet and greeting and looking like a painting.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 411, "question": "So if you could give advice to that young dancing girl we just saw, what would you tell her?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 412, "answer": "Well, I was so busy working then that I couldn't think.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 466, "question": "Are you ready?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 467, "answer": "OK.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 472, "question": "Or a pen?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 473, "answer": "OK.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 479, "question": "-- you like that?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 480, "answer": "(INAUDIBLE).", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 486, "question": "All right, do you get your blood pressure checked annually?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 487, "answer": "Yes, well, sometimes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "CD", "TO", "CD", "IN", "CC", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 490, "question": "Do you know your blood pressure?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 491, "answer": "AUPER: It usually sits around -- I don't know, 60 to 80 below or above.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 507, "question": "Do you have doctors look in your mouth at all?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 508, "answer": "Yes, when I go to the dentist.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 523, "question": "Yes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 524, "answer": "-- it's representative of the globalization of medicine.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 562, "question": "A new mom?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 563, "answer": "I know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", ",", "NNS", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ":", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ":", "."], "qSentId": 566, "question": "And you have another one that's three?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "CD", "WDT", "VBZ", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 567, "answer": "Three, yes, my daughter Leila (ph) and my son Emmitt (ph).", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 572, "question": "And go back to -- to being your old self?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "RB", "TO", ":", "IN", "VBG", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 573, "answer": "You know, it's -- it's pretty amazing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 580, "question": "You know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 581, "answer": "Well, let me ask you a question.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 582, "question": "You -- you took the real age test, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 583, "answer": "I did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 585, "question": "You have?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 586, "answer": "About five years ago.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "CD", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 588, "question": "Z: Well, what's your real age?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 589, "answer": "My real age is 37.9 or something.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 621, "question": "Were you nervous about getting pregnant that late?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "VBG", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 622, "answer": "I didn't feel nervous.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 644, "question": "What's a typical breakfast you might have?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 645, "answer": "Every day, I have two breakfasts.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 657, "question": "What do you do to protect your eyes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 658, "answer": "I put drops in my eyes when I'm traveling because I have to keep them moist.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 669, "question": "Do you have mommy brain at all?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 670, "answer": "I thought I didn't, but I think I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 706, "question": "You did research and that's true, that men digest quicker than women?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NN", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 707, "answer": "Not all things, but we're specifically talking about Ambien type drugs.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 714, "question": "Think about it, what is sleep really telling you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 715, "answer": "You're tired.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 729, "question": "And are you a good sleeper?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 730, "answer": "I am not a great sleeper.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 753, "question": "You'll dream of something that then happens in real life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NN", "WDT", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 754, "answer": "Yeah, yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 759, "question": "What do you do to sleep better?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 760, "answer": "I try -- this is such an old lady thing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 763, "question": "Is that true?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 764, "answer": "No question.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 768, "question": "How is sleep for you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 769, "answer": "Sleep is actually fine.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 779, "question": "A power nap?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 780, "answer": "In fact, when I was pregnant with my daughter, I would carry ear plugs with me in my car.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 783, "question": "You never got arrested?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 784, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 786, "question": "Question for all three of you, do any of you take sleep medications?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "DT", "CD", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 787, "answer": "I sometimes take melatonin.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", ",", "RB", "TO", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 788, "question": "Melatonin?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 789, "answer": "Because -- but you know, a natural doc told me once to take 20 milligrams of it, up to 20.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 829, "question": "Toothpaste?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 830, "answer": "Toothpaste have other things in them, but I don't know if -- I haven't seen it in there.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 841, "question": "Do you keep track of these different things in literature, Madeleine?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 842, "answer": "I don't think about them.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Madeleine"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 860, "question": "Are you worried about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 861, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 884, "question": "What's that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 885, "answer": "Z: It's a chemical compound that is linked to all kinds of bad stuff, including cancer.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 893, "question": "Like is there -- can you -- is that safe to think or is that crazy to think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "VBZ", "EX", ":", "MD", "PRP", ":", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 894, "answer": "It's rational to think.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 910, "question": "How does that -- Lisa, how does it make you feel younger or live longer?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", ":", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "JJR", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 911, "answer": "It's funny.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Lisa"]}}]